Finding Aid for the Edwin Eustace Reinke Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Edwin Eustace Reinke Collection
multiple
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0362
.42 linear_feet
- Fairfield from the back (photo)
- Br. Clemens (photo)
- E.E. R., 1 Sept. 1862 (photo)
- Edwin M. Stanton (photo)
- New Carmel (photo)
- New Bethel in Jamaica, by A.A.R. (drawing)
- Br. Lind and unident. women (drawings)
- Br. Sonderman & the Normal School Class (photo)
- A breadfruit tree (photo)
- A young plantain tree (photo)
- New Carmel, from the pasture (photo)
- Beaufort, Jamaica (photo)
- Sherman House (hotel), Chicago, Aug. 30, 186-, receipt to Mr. Reinke
- Russell House (hotel), Detroit, Aug. 29, 1865, receipt to Mr. Reinke
- New Carmel pulpit (photo)
- Drawing: ink and stone with number 40: "I'll raise my Ebenezer here: The LORD has help'd thus far." Aug. 12, 1831.
- Dr. Leinbach & wife (photo)
- Brooklyn Church (photo)
- Mr. Seward (photo)
- Gov. Martin (photo
- Cataract House, Niagara Falls, 28 August 1865, receipt
- Willard's Hotel, Washington, 30 July 1850, receipt
- Mansion House, Philadelphia, 19 Oct. 1859, to E. E. Reinke, receipt
- Bennett & Co., n.d., receipt
- E.L.H., Aet. 28, June 24, 1828 (drawing)
- Emma Maria Augusta Reinke, Age 2 y ½ (cut-out silhouette)
- Amadeus, about 1836 (said to be) (drawing)
- E'.E.R., about 1836 (said to be) (drawing)
- A Greenland Man, House and Seal (drawing)
- A Greenland Woman, Tent and Birds (drawing)
- A Greenlander in His Kajak, in pursuit of a seal. (drawing)
- Profile of a Greenland House, containing 3 families (drawing)
- Greenland Women's Boat (drawing)
- Gracehill, Antigua (drawing)
- Cedarhill, Antigua (drawing)
- Gracebay, Antigua (drawing)
- Bishop Reinke, April 1863 (photo)
- A silly group (photo)
- Document: Bethlehem, Northampton Co., Penna., August 28, 1862; Office of the U.S. Deputy Marshal: Edwin E. Reinke is "enrolled as a citizen" and "liable to Military Service"
- James Nick (?) (photo)
- Document: Centennial Jubilee, Moravian Mission, Jamaica, 7 Dec. 1854
- Photos: Br. Knauss, E.E.R. (2), Br. Hagen, Sr. Zorn, Dr. Martin, Clemens Zoebisch, Miss Benigna Smythe, Miss Martha Smythe, Amadeus, Aug. 1862, Br. Heydenreich, Br. F. Wolle, Sr. Lichtenthaler, Br. Ernest Bleek, Miss Fanny Langdon, Miss Georgiana Harvey, Keokuk (Isaac J. Fox, chief, in Kansas), unid, ladies.
- A number of other photographs, chiefly of Civil War period military and political figures, have been removed, with only handwritten captions to Indicate their previous presence. Most of the rest of the contents of the scrapbook are made up of clippings, articles and engravings, relating to the Civil War, scenes in various parts of the world, and a few religious and sentimental items.